The case we're
about to show you
today was a
difficult one to
make. Because what
happened on April
6, 2022 was so
tragic that it
deeply affected our
team. I mean, that
day was like, I'd
just seen him keep
freckles and it's
like, funny, 😂 happy
disposition. And it
was gone. And for
sure, my mind 🤯 could
not wrap itself
around that. I
still cannot
believe he's gone.
Little Eli had just
returned home 🏠 from
school when his mom
surprised him with
his new debit card.
He had spent a
long time ⏰ saving
the money he earned
from shoveling and
mowing jobs, and he
was finally ready
to spend it. He
was beyond excited
and immediately
wanted to buy some
treats from a
nearby grocery
store. His mom told
him they could go
together that
evening, but Eli
couldn't contain
his excitement.
Eventually, she
allowed him to make
the trip on his
own, and being the
responsible little
boy he was, Eli
took his bike and
put on his helmet
before heading to
the store. Once he
had bought his
treats, he began
riding back home.